

Wahab Anjum

Full stack web app developer

Hard Skills

Front-end

Angular Framework

Typescript

Javascript

Ngrx *

Jasmine

Rxis

CSS

SASS *

Bootstrap

Html

VCS / Others

Git

GitHub

Scrum *

Back-end

.NET Core / Asp.NET

C#

Firebase

MVC

LINQ

MSSQL

Cloud

Azure Firebase smarterasp.net Netlify I am a passionate self-taught fullstack developer with almost 2 years of experience in PWAs development, focused on writing performant code using best practices and learning new technologies. My main area of expertise is resolving complex algorithms using Angular and Rxjs. I am a fast learner, perseverant, analytical and with result oriented mindset. portfolio: pikuman.dev

Professional Experience

Full stack web app Developer - Freelance July 2020 - Present

For: BB for Investors

- Portfolio for Real Estate investors / Sept 21
 - Multi-language "Serverless" site with total autonomy for the client to add, edit or delete their projects (dynamically categorized in separate tabs) and news, upload photos, create users, personalized quotations & dashboards.
 - Angular, Firebase authentication, storage and Firestore cloud...

For: MB Tech

- Financial Reporting & Business analytical dashboard app / Jan 21 -Mar 21
 - Financial Reporting & Business analytical dashboard app
 - Angular, ASP.NET, SAP Crystal Reports, IIS hosting...
- ERP / Jul 20 Dec 20
 - An ERP which integrates Finance, Purchase, Sales & Production departments and provide 50+ reports for full business control.
 - Angular, .NET Core, ASP.NET, SAP Crystal Reports, IIS hosting...
 Detailed summary in Portfolio (link at the bottom)

Barceló Hotels Group

May 2006 - Present

Several departments

- · Managing individual bookings and quotations
- Client attention through email, phone and in person
- · New staff training
- Event Organizing
- · Providing services in several F&B departments

IDEs / Libraries

VS Code Visual Studio MSSQL Management Studio Angular Material Ngx Charts

(*) Theoretical knowledge

Soft Skills

Organized & Self-demanding

Problem solving

Experienced teamworker

Analytical mindset

Hard-worker

Languages

Spanish: Professional

Proficiency

English: Advanced

Catalan: Intermediate

Urdu/Hindi: Native

Punjabi: Native

Contact

ô

Barcelona - Spain



(+34) 600 731 531

@

wahab_anjum[at]hotmai l.com

Education

Current focus

- Learning Scrum from Cibernarium Barcelona Activa
- Jasmine learning and testing on my recent project
- Enhancing my knowledge of Rxjs operators and looking forward to learn Ngrx and SASS

MDN Docs

May 2020 - July 2020

Studied the complete tutorial 'Become a Front-End Developer'

Intermediate in Computer Science September 1999 - March 2001

Govt Murray Collage - Sialkot, Pakistan

- All the optional subjects were related to finance & statistics
- Co-founded a tech company "MB-TECH". Participated in multiple projects as a member

Interests

- · Keeping me up-to-date with new technologies
- Committee member of Barcelona ultimate frisbee club. Playing and training students.
- Playing badminton and Padel
- Other interests: hiking, skiing, arcade games, running and cycling

Links

Portfolio:

pikuman.dev

Linkedin:

https://linkedin.com/in/wahab-anjum-47497675

Latest project analysis:

• Proposal: pikuman.dev/argonia

Latest Project:

- BB for Investors, Dummy-url: https://bbinvestors.netlify.app
- Proposal: pikuman.dev/propuestaBB
- Github: https://github.com/pikuman83/bbInvestors